MOBILE APP DEVELOPER

Jawaid Ali Mangi

PROFILE

Experienced Mobile app developer who has a track record of success creating app that are both well-received and commercially viable. Experience in software development lifecycle (SDLC) including analysis ,design, development, testing and deployment Skilled as team player as well developed some of big projects individually. Strong eye for details and tenacity to never quit on something until it is absolutely perfect.

EXPERIENCE

MOBILE APP DEVELOPER: AUZWARE SOLUTIONS – JAN-2022-PRESENT Casino Reward App (IOS, Android) for a Casino in USA.

Equipment Management (IOS, Android) Florida Equipment Rental Company USA.

Sign Language App ML (Android) Detect sign language teach sign language.

MOBILE APP DEVELOPER: ZEPTA CONSULTING TECH – 2021-2022 JAN Attendance System (IOS and Android) Gps and multi Role based.

Movies App for (IOS, Android) available on play store.

Fitness App for (IOS, Android)

ANDROID DEVELOPER: FREELANCE SOURCE - 2019-2021

Developed Leo Browser available on play store

Developed various small projects related University Tasks Projects Assignment

Using Java(Android) Sqlite, Firebase,

EDUCATION

Iqra University: Karachi-Pakistan – BS(SE), 2021 APRIL

SKILLS

- Flutter (IOS, Android)
- Java(Android)
- Android Studio
- MVVM, BLOC,GET, Providers
- Firebase, Gitlab, Github, Xcode
- Push Notifications, Authentication, Realtime Database
- Sqlite, Graphql, Room,